http://www.mbionline.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Access to Our WebsiteMaster Builders of Iowa is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website. You are free to access and browse our site without disclosing personal data, and you can be assured that we will protect the confidentiality and security of your information at all times.We do not release any information to outside parties without the express permission of our website users. In addition, Master Builders of Iowa fully complies with HIPAA privacy regulations.Information CollectionMaster Builders of Iowa does not automatically collect personal information from our website nor do we use cookies to store personal information. We do not link personal information about specific individuals with any other information we collect, either on our website or in our facilities.We do not collect personal information from other sources such as public records or private databases nor do we release or sell personal information about those who access our website.We do collect personal information that is voluntarily provided while using our services. All privacy practices and regulations apply to this information, as well.Confidentiality and SecurityMaster Builders of Iowa does not disclose personal information to other organizations.We ensure that personal information will not be disclosed to federal or state institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.We have instituted technical measures to protect personal information in our files from unauthorized access; improper use or disclosure; unauthorized modification, or unlawful destruction or accidental loss.All Master Builders of Iowa employees who have access to and who process personal information are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of the information.Our website does provide access to additional information with links to other sites. It is our hope that these sites offer privacy protection, but Master Builders of Iowa is not responsible for their content or privacy practices.Contact InformationIf you have questions or need further information about Master Builders of Iowa's privacy/legal statement, please call (515) 288-8904 or email info@mbi.build.
Master Builders of Iowa
About
Staff
Leadership
Annual Report
INSIDEMBI
Videos
Get Involved
MBI AFFILIATED SITES:
